[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "title": "Memory Items",
    "CardStack": [
      {
      "id": 0,
      "Front": "Cabin Altitude Hi",
      "Back": "Oxygen Masks - Don w/ 100% Oxygen, Crew Communications - Establish",
      },
      {
      "id": 1,
      "Front": "Engine Abnormal Start",
      "Back": "Affected Engine: Start/Stop Selector - STOP",
      },
      {
      "id": 2,
      "Front": "Smoke Evacuation",
      "Back": "Oxygen Masks: Don Emergency, Crew Communication: Establish, Pressurization Dump: Push In",
      },
      {
      "id": 3,
      "Front": "Smoke/Fire/Fumes",
      "Back": "Oxygen Masks: Don with 100% oxygen, Crew Communication: Establish",
      },
      {
      "id": 4,
      "Front": "Batt 1 (2) Overtemp",
      "Back": "Associated Battery: OFF",
      },
      {
      "id": 5,
      "Front": "Jammed Control Wheel - Roll",
      "Back": "Aileron Disconnect Handle: Pull",
      },
      {
      "id": 6,
      "Front": "Jammed Control Column - Pitch",
      "Back": "Elevator Disconnect Handle: Pull",
      },
      {
      "id": 7,
      "Front": "Pitch Trim Runaway",
      "Back": "A/P Disconnect Button: Press and Hold, Pitch Trim Sys 1 & 2 Cutout Buttons: Push In",
      },
      {
      "id": 8,
      "Front": "Roll (Yaw) Trim Runaway",
      "Back": "A/P Disconnect Button: Press and Hold",
      },
      {
      "id": 9,
      "Front": "Steering Runaway",
      "Back": "Steer Disconnect Switch: Press. steer the airplane using differential braking and rudder.",
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "title": "Weight Limitations",
    "CardStack": [
        {
        "id": 0,
        "Front": "Max Ramp Weight - 76 PAX ",
        "Back": "85,870 lb"
        },
        {
        "id": 1,
        "Front": "Max Takeoff Weight - 76 PAX",
        "Back": "85,517 lb"
        },
        {
        "id": 2,
        "Front": "Max Landing Weight - 76 PAX",
        "Back": "74,957 lb"
        },
        {
        "id": 3,
        "Front": "Max Zero Fuel Weight - 76 PAX",
        "Back": "69,886 lb"
        },
        {
        "id": 4,
        "Front": "Max Ramp Weight - 70 PAX ",
        "Back": "85,540 lb"
        },
        {
        "id": 5,
        "Front": "Max Takeoff Weight - 70 PAX",
        "Back": "85,098 lb"
        },
        {
        "id": 6,
        "Front": "Max Landing Weight - 70 PAX",
        "Back": "74,957 lb"
        },
        {
        "id": 7,
        "Front": "Max Zero Fuel Weight - 70 PAX",
        "Back": "69,467 lb"
        },
        {
        "id": 8,
        "Front": "Min Runway Width",
        "Back": "100 ft"
        },
        {
        "id": 9,
        "Front": "Wing Span",
        "Back": "93 ft 11 in"
        },
        {
        "id": 10,
        "Front": "Aircraft Length",
        "Back": "103 ft 11 in"
        },
        {
        "id": 11,
        "Front": "Tail Height",
        "Back": "32 ft 4 in"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "title": "Operational Limitations",
      "CardStack": [
        {
          "id": 0,
          "Front": "Max Operational Altitude",
          "Back": "41,000 ft"
        },
        {
          "id": 1,
          "Front": "Max Takeoff & Landing Altitude",
          "Back": "8,000 ft"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "Front": "Max Temperature Takeoff & Landing",
          "Back": "ISA + 35 C or 52 F"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "Front": "Min Temperature Takeoff & Landing",
          "Back": "-40 C"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "Front": "Runway Slope Limitation",
          "Back": "+/- 2%"
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "Front": "Max Tailwind",
          "Back": "15 kts"
        },
        {
          "id": 6,
          "Front": "Max Single Pack Operations",
          "Back": "31,000 ft"
        },
        {
          "id": 7,
          "Front": "Vmo SL - 8000 ft",
          "Back": "300"
        },
        {
          "id": 8,
          "Front": "Vmo 10,000 - Mach Transition",
          "Back": "320"
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "Front": "Mmo",
          "Back": "0.82"
        },
        {
          "id": 10,
          "Front": "VA",
          "Back": "240"
        },
        {
          "id": 11,
          "Front": "VLO extend",
          "Back": "250"
        },
        {
          "id": 12,
          "Front": "VLO retract",
          "Back": "3250"
        },
        {
          "id": 13,
          "Front": "VLE",
          "Back": "250"
        },
        {
          "id": 14,
          "Front": "V tire",
          "Back": "195"
        },
        {
          "id": 15,
          "Front": "V RAT Deploy Max",
          "Back": "Vmo/Mmo"
        },
        {
          "id": 16,
          "Front": "Vmin To provide Electrical Power (RAT)",
          "Back": "130"
        },
        {
          "id": 17,
          "Front": "Vb (below 10,000 ft)",
          "Back": "250"
        },
        {
          "id": 18,
          "Front": "Vb (10,000 ft and above)",
          "Back": "270/0.76M (whichever is lower)"
        },
        {
          "id": 19,
          "Front": "V wiper ops ",
          "Back": "250"
        },
        {
          "id": 20,
          "Front": "V window",
          "Back": "160"
        },
        {
          "id": 21,
          "Front": "Vfe 1",
          "Back": "230"
        },
        {
          "id": 22,
          "Front": "Vfe 2",
          "Back": "215"
        },
        {
          "id": 23,
          "Front": "Vfe 3",
          "Back": "200"
        },
        {
          "id": 24,
          "Front": "Vfe 4",
          "Back": "180"
        },
        {
          "id": 25,
          "Front": "Vfe 5",
          "Back": "180"
        },
        {
          "id": 26,
          "Front": "V FULL",
          "Back": "165"
        },
        {
          "id": 27,
          "Front": "Dry Max Crosswind",
          "Back": "38 kt"
        },
        {
          "id": 28,
          "Front": "Wet Max Crosswind",
          "Back": "31 kt"
        },
        {
          "id": 29,
          "Front": "Runway with Compacted Snow Max Crosswind",
          "Back": "20 kt"
        },
        {
          "id": 30,
          "Front": "Runway with Standing Water/Slush/Wet Snow/Dry Snow Max Crosswind",
          "Back": "18 kt"
        },
        {
          "id": 31,
          "Front": "Runway with Ice Max Crosswind",
          "Back": "12 kt"
        },
        {
          "id": 32,
          "Front": "Static Crosswind Max Crosswind",
          "Back": "30 kts"
        },
        {
          "id": 33,
          "Front": "Max Altitude for Flaps and Slats to be Extended",
          "Back": "20,000 ft"
        },
        {
          "id": 34,
          "Front": "Enroute Altitude for Slats and Flaps",
          "Back": "Prohibited"
        },
        {
          "id": 35,
          "Front": "Min Spoiler Speed",
          "Back": "180 kts"
        },
        {
          "id": 36,
          "Front": "Flap Setting - Cat II Approach ",
          "Back": "Mandatory Flaps 5"
        },
        {
          "id": 37,
          "Front": "Missed Approach Flap Setting - Flaps Full",
          "Back": "Flaps 4"
        },
        {
          "id": 38,
          "Front": "Missed Approach Flap Setting - Flaps 5",
          "Back": "Flaps 2"
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "title": "System Limitations",
      "CardStack": [
        {
          "id": 0,
          "Front": "Min Battery Voltage",
          "Back": "22.5 V"
        },
        {
          "id": 1,
          "Front": "Max Engine Temp",
          "Back": "815 C"
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "title": "All Limitations",
      "CardStack": [
        {
          "id": 0,
          "Front": "Min Battery Voltage",
          "Back": "22.5 V"
        },
        {
          "id": 1,
          "Front": "Max Engine Temp",
          "Back": "815 C"
        },
      ]
    }
  }
]
